Eyad Hisham

I'm a Software Engineer, I worked in many development roles such as developer, business analyst, project manager, product owner and even account manager.

I created many commercial apps in wide variety of platforms/industries/domains.

I have built 6+ commercial mobile apps, 200+ Photoshop scripts and 8+ commercial web systems.

Contact

Address:

Egypt, cairo, nasr city

Phone:

+20 11 000 99039

Email:

eyiadhisham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ey-ha96

Github:

github.com/xEyad

Portfolio (images)

Online CV

Technical demos

Visual pathfinder

Algorithm visualizer

C++ Chess game (exe)

Dynamic widgets builder

Elapsed circle

Technical tools

- Flutter
- Angular 5+
- JavaScript
- CSS/SCSS
- Typescript
- Dart
- C++ 14
- C++ 11
- AHK
- QT
- React

Languages

English – B2 Arabic - Native

Experience

CrossWorkers – software engineer

- Amesto Oslo, Norway (web) 4/2023 Present Building a tool that helps companies submit their sustainability report
- QPR Helsinki, Finland (web) 05/2022- 4/2023 Working With QPR SOFTWARE on the new gen of Strategy management software that serves big companies and public sector using React as frontend framework
 - Created performance tracking software for government entities using React, Redux, Material UI.
 - Implemented a web-based PowerPoint-like feature for creating complex dashboards using React and Highcharts with the ability to export to PDF and PowerPoint.

Fabrica dev – software engineer

01/2019 - 05/2022

• Waterway (web,ios,android)

Worked on Waterway internal web system. designed and implemented it's EOI module. Also, built it's mobile app using flutter. "Waterway" is a major realestate developer in Egypt and the solution manages their internal CRM system.

O Castle developments (web,ios,android)

Worked on Castle developments internal web system, designed and implemented their helpdesk system and built its **mobile app** that manages their internal CRM and units' reservations using **flutter**

JD Holdings (web)

Worked on JD Holdings internal web system. This system is used by all 4 major developers under the parent company JD Holdings.

RE/MAX Egypt (web)

Designed, developed and deployed RE/MAX Egypt internal CRM system that operates and manage the

leads coming from the <u>CAPTOUR</u> project and distributing it to sub RE/MAX offices/franchises.

O Connect homes (web)

Designed, developed and deployed the internal **web** system and **mobile app**, connect homes is

Eyad Hisham

I'm a Software Engineer, I worked in many development roles such as developer, business analyst, project manager, product owner and even account manager.

I created many commercial apps in wide variety of platforms/industries/domains.

I have built 6+ commercial mobile apps, 200+ Photoshop scripts and 8+ commercial web systems.

Contact

Address:

Egypt, cairo, nasr city

Phone:

+20 11 000 99039

Email:

eyiadhisham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ey-ha96

Github:

github.com/xEyad

Portfolio (images)

Online CV

Technical demos

Visual pathfinder

Algorithm visualizer

C++ Chess game (exe)

Dynamic widgets builder

Elapsed circle

Technical tools

- Flutter
- Angular 5+
- JavaScript
- CSS/SCSS
- Typescript
- Dart
- C++ 14
- C++ 11
- AHK
- QT
- React

Languages

English – B2 Arabic - Native

Experience

Psycoders – software engineer

Project based

O Diet academy (web,ios,android)

Worked on Diet academy web dashboard and built its **mobile app.** Diet academy is solution that enables users to reserve video or chat packages with the doctor and maintain patient information.

Bondo (ios,android)

Worked on Bondo web dashboard and Built its **mobile app.** Bondo is a small scale social media that operates over the map, where user can record a voicenote and add some metadata to it. then it will be shown over the google map and other users can interact with it.

NewGame (web)

Built NewGame e-commerce website. NewGame is boardgames manufacturer and distributor in egypt.

Egyptian Veterinarians syndicate (ios, android)
Built Egyptian vets syndicate mobile app.

• Venu (ios, android, waiter app)

Built Venu dine in mobile app and its two main components. The client facing app and the waiter pos tablet app

Fiverr - Photoshop Automator (freelance) 01/2017 - present

O Photoshop scripts

Successfully created and delivered over 200 photoshop script and automation solutions to 100+ client in more than 16 country

Education

B.Sc. computer science

2013-2017

- Higher technological institute (HTI)
- GPA: 3.0